[{"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He described Allawi 's face as that of a f*ed horse and he dismissed the whole government as a band of thieves and traitors .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dismissed\", does the participant \"government\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We were told that we could n't today because they were closing soon .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"closing\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Bredders take the one that in not very interested and put it alone in a breeeding tank for 3 - 5 days .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"take\", does the participant \"Bredders\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"There is NO such thing as a BTA .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"thing\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We came at around 730 and they close at 8 and wanted to try the specials but they were out for the day so I would say go way before they close .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"close\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This BuzzMachine post argues that Google 's rush toward ubiquity might backfire -- which we 've all heard before , but it 's particularly well - put in this post .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"backfire\", does the participant \"rush\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He told us to stop by the salon and then he will tell us the price .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"us\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Disney cruises offer 24 - hour room services , and the crews are ready to serve you the way you like .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"offer\", does the participant \"cruises\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I love this cage , it 's easy to clean , very spacious and fun for the hamster\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"It is our belief that this compensation plan will produce some of the largest checks in network marketing history .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"produce\", does the participant \"plan\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Last June , an international initiative led by Japan to persuade the LTTE to come back to the negotiating table failed despite an aid package offer of US$ 4.5 billion .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"failed\", does the participant \"initiative\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have to say the value of this place always amazes me .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"amazes\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Louisiana 's Governor Blanco urged residents to spend Wednesday in prayer and assured them the crisis would eventually be overcome .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"urged\", does the participant \"Blanco\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I doubt he will be extradited to Venezuela , which is the only way that question could be answered with a Yes .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"extradited\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Upon the same day he conquered Darius , won a great victory at sea , & died the same day .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"conquered\", does the participant \"Darius\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This place had the worst tasting pizza I have ever tasted it was possible the worst food I 've ever eaten .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tasted\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The classes cover all age and skill ranges , with BALLROOM , LATIN , SEQUENCE , STREET , DISCO , LINE DANCING , BALLET , TAP & JAZZ .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cover\", does the participant \"ranges\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Many online stores carry them , like Adorama :\"\nQuestion: In the event \"carry\", does the participant \"stores\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We tried 4 different style of donuts , they were all the same when it came to quality .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tried\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They took on the challenge of making my Ferrari all I dreamed of and more .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dreamed\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They were from all accounts marginalized and not listened to .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"marginalized\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I believe that these are three weekends in a row , January 6 , 13 and 20th .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"believe\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Chahine said her immediate family spent about $ 20,000 to return to Detroit via Syria and Jordan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"spent\", does the participant \"$\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"She forwarded the Sommer letter to Stan and discussed it with him .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"forwarded\", does the participant \"letter\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Michele Tollis , Fabio 's father , began to attend metal concerts and festivals across Europe , handing out leaflets and quizzing Fabio 's friends .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"began\", does the participant \"Tollis\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"As faith leaders , we commit ourselves to public action , visibility , education , and mutual support in the service of the right and freedom to marry .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"commit\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He responded \" we have problem with ' people ' \" .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"responded\", does the participant \"He\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I called and got the same runaround on hold and noone calls you back .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"called\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Her husband became a citizen of the US just the week before last .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"became\", does the participant \"husband\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" You say , ' wow ! '\"\nQuestion: In the event \"say\", does the participant \"You\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I want to use this opportunity to welcome Brian Ryner to Google !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"welcome\", does the participant \"Ryner\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I enjoyed the animations and wanted to share them with my friends .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"share\", does the participant \"them\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Bradley 's record of 300 phenophases found that even prior to 1999 , spring was arriving in higher latitudes several weeks earlier than in the earlier years of her data .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"arriving\", does the participant \"spring\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"As faith leaders , we commit ourselves to public action , visibility , education , and mutual support in the service of the right and freedom to marry .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"commit\", does the participant \"ourselves\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I know that with my industry - wide and investment banking contacts that I can help raise capital for the fund .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"know\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They told me that this is not under warranty and want to charge me $ 175 just to diagnose the problem !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"On my panel , Loretta Lynch asked Reliant and Duke to supply her with the details of the contracts they cut to sell their power forward to marketers .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"supply\", does the participant \"her\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My last rabbit did that a few times , and he was fine ...\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"rabbit\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They wish to launch on Sept. 1 - meaning we will need to be sending mailings sometime around mid-August .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wish\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"You need to check out the French Indochina War ( 1946 - 1954 ) not the Vietnam War ( 1957 - 1975 ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"check\", does the participant \"War\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I enjoyed working with all of you during the past five years at Enron / Azurix , and I wish you all of the best .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wish\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Musk , which is scraped from their genitals once a day for as long as they can surv ive , makes the scent of perfume last a bit longer after each application .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"makes\", does the participant \"Musk\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Dr. Wallen explained the procedure in detail and took his time with me .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"explained\", does the participant \"Wallen\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The situation appears to be even worse in Mississippi .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"appears\", does the participant \"situation\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I ran into Corey last night at LW s and I am thinking this is a girl for Darren .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ran\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I called over the weekend due to clogged kitchen sink .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"called\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" There is always the possibility they could jam us up , make us look like we are not numero uno , \" Pike said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"jam\", does the participant \"us\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"they all need love and attn , food , proper surroundings etc .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Peter Dale Scott includes an account of how Terrell 's whistleblowing was stifled by them in his book Cocaine Politics .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"stifled\", does the participant \"whistleblowing\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Dessert was ... hmmm , that 's interesting , I do n't even remember dessert .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remember\", does the participant \"dessert\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I want to party hardy for my birthday :)\"\nQuestion: In the event \"want\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The money funds their travel , explosives , hideouts and permanent search for soft vulnerable targets .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"funds\", does the participant \"money\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have no doubt that the rescue is wonderful .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My wife has a slight impediment in her speech .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"impediment\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" They can freely write anything they like about our prophet , but if one raises doubts about the Holocaust he is either fined or sent to prison , \" he added .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"write\", does the participant \"anything\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have no complaints about the service I received .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"complaints\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I think that this is for you since I do n't know any of these people .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The last I checked , the Satanists have a long way to go to catch up with the death and destruction dealt out by self - proclaimed ( though false ) Christians .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"checked\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In Baghdad Kadhim Talal Husain , assistant dean at the School of Education at Mustansiriyah University , was assassinated with his driver in the Salikh district .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assassinated\", does the participant \"Husain\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Enron continues to feel free to move me around at will .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"continues\", does the participant \"Enron\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"By comparison , outdoor cats have a life expectancy of 3 - 7 years depending on how many predators are in the local environment .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"cats\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a concern that the Enron optionality bug could bite us on the backside with that one .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"concern\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I found an injured pure white bird ( dove I guess ? )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"guess\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I promise you that if you follow the directions exactly that you will start making more money than you thought possible by doing something so easy !!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"follow\", does the participant \"directions\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A lack of organisation , coupled with the distain for its customers , makes this the worst rental agency I have used .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"makes\", does the participant \"this\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I was amazed at the spiel they delivered .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"delivered\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Guerrillas threatened to assassinate Prime Minister Iyad Allawi and Minister of Defense Hazem Shaalan in retaliation for the attack .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"threatened\", does the participant \"Guerrillas\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Yeah you got ta burn it .. that s the only way\"\nQuestion: In the event \"got\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I ordered a kid meal with a milk and found a bottle was half opened already .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ordered\", does the participant \"meal\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I believe the message you forwarded to me belongs to the Mark Taylor at EI ( based in London ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"forwarded\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The painting is based upon the hymn called , ' A Charge to Keep . '\"\nQuestion: In the event \"based\", does the participant \"painting\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"That 's overstating it , I know .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"know\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have 3 children there and they are the Best .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"children\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"She gave me amazing pictures at an amazing price and made my wedding day so memorable .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"gave\", does the participant \"She\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a new born daughter and she helped me with a lot .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"daughter\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Only Irish coffee provides in a single glass all four essential food groups : alcohol , caffeine , sugar and fat .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"provides\", does the participant \"coffee\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have the opportunity to pick up a super nice 6 year old for free .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"His one - day mission vaulted his communist homeland into the elite circle of spacefaring nations - Russia and the United States - that can launch and sustain humans in space .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"launch\", does the participant \"humans\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"But the menu had standard stuff that one would get at a Belgian Tavern .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"menu\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The next day , the federal commission killed the new pricing plan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"plan\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I did an overnight in a home stay that was sweet and the water market was wonderful .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He refused to believe them and ordered the military to win the war within two to three years ( before the next election in 1968 ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"believe\", does the participant \"them\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Senator Patrick Leahy at a Congressional hearing in the Spring of 2002 noted that the FBI had collected the Ames strain from 20 sources .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"noted\", does the participant \"Leahy\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Your buddy Beau invited me .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"invited\", does the participant \"buddy\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My last rabbit did that a few times , and he was fine ...\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"that\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My cat had a seizure yesterday and was ill .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"cat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Jana made me feel very comfortable .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"made\", does the participant \"Jana\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They provide an emotional infrastructure for atrocities .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"provide\", does the participant \"infrastructure\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"US - trained Malaysian biochemist Yazid Sufaat met with 9/11 plotters and two hijackers in January 2000 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"met\", does the participant \"Sufaat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I enjoyed my tour and i am looking for adventure tour and India heritage tours for valuable .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"enjoyed\", does the participant \"tour\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I know that we address audit rights in the LLC agreement so this may not matter anyway if this is a right they already have .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"know\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"It is rumored that North Korea has at least a couple nuclear weapons .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"rumored\", does the participant \"It\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Today 's incident proves that Sharon has lost his patience and his hope in peace .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"lost\", does the participant \"patience\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I did the work myself for $ 50 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Chahine said her immediate family spent about $ 20,000 to return to Detroit via Syria and Jordan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"spent\", does the participant \"family\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The S100 has a slightly larger screen and the new digic 5 processor .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"screen\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The office refused my requests to see what they got from BC / BS .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"refused\", does the participant \"office\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"At the time , guardsmen were required to accumulate a minimum of 50 points to meet their yearly obligation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"meet\", does the participant \"obligation\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"U.S. President George W. Bush shakes hands with Chinese President Hu Jintao in a bilateral meeting in Santiago .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"shakes\", does the participant \"Bush\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We are resolved that the State should not interfere with same - gender couples who choose to marry and share fully and equally in the rights , responsibilities , and commitments of civil marriage .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"choose\", does the participant \"couples\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They did that with no problem .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Security in the hotel seemed to be excellent , but we were never given an explanation as to why someone would open these items .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"open\", does the participant \"someone\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I urge all St. Thomas the Apostle parishioners and all of South Florida residents to come see Gus !!!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"urge\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We had to throw out about 80 percent of our meals because the food tasted so horrible .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"throw\", does the participant \"percent\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I apologize , I 'm on the road and have n't heard when that will be .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"apologize\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Jim Lobe has more on the political implications of the Fallujah assault , both in Iraq and in Washington .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"Lobe\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A team from the court managed to take his deposition before he died .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They came to my house in no time and started working on the gate .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"came\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I knew a cat that died in its sleep aged 21 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"cat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Michael helped shoot the majority of my firm 's website and we could not have been happier .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"helped\", does the participant \"Michael\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This type of harness goes around the dog s chest and legs and has a clip for the leash up on the back of the dog in middle of shoulder blades .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"goes\", does the participant \"type\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A little birdie told me that you were checking into tickets for Seoul .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"checking\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He gave no indication on the value of the highest bid .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"gave\", does the participant \"He\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I had no problem with my delivery .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"problem\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a Norwegian Forest Cat that is named Achilles bc as a kitten he always attacked your feet when you walked by !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"attacked\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"But they remain uncertain about whether China aims to beat the United States to the moon in its secretive space effort .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remain\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"You have two adjustment screws for up and down and right to left positions .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"screws\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A little birdie told me that you were checking into tickets for Seoul .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Cities such as Falluja received special treatment from Saddam and enjoyed a disproportionate share of the country 's wealth and power .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"received\", does the participant \"treatment\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I sent a graphic that would have been distorted if printed as it was .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sent\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I suspect the streets of Baghdad will look as if a war is looming this week .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"suspect\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I love them !!!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I took the original piece of metal and rigged it to make due since I had to complete the job .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"complete\", does the participant \"job\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" Iran has significant capabilities for asymmetric warfare , and poses the additional threat of proliferation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"Iran\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"( I think there are close to 24,000 groups )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I thought that I had gained my cockatiel 's trust , but now he 's not coming to me when I open his cage .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"thought\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" At some point , Patricia tripped or the bear tripped her and was at her back .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tripped\", does the participant \"her\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We love our new roof !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"roof\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I see that we are scheduled to have lunch today .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"scheduled\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"ALITO filed a dissenting opinion , in which SCALIA and THOMAS joined as to Parts I through III .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"filed\", does the participant \"ALITO\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I started collecting animations & jokes just to help with my boredom and depression .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"started\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Secretive efforts keep outsiders in the dark about the program 's goals\"\nQuestion: In the event \"keep\", does the participant \"outsiders\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I came to find out the person was the hotel OWNER also .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"came\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We love everything about the fence .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They kept the name Oracle and created the RDBMS engine .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"created\", does the participant \"engine\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The bear dwarfed the 6 - foot - 1 Mr. Parenteau , knocking him to the ground , he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dwarfed\", does the participant \"Parenteau\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"But today , I got a boy and realized that he is HUGE !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"got\", does the participant \"boy\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Within seven days , I started getting money in the mail !!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"started\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He needs more info about these trades ( i.e. , price info ) and would like to talk with you about it .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"needs\", does the participant \"info\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"First room had used tissues next to the bed and I requested it be rectified .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"requested\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My car broke down and roadside towed my vehicle to Sussman Kia .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"broke\", does the participant \"car\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They came on time and completed their work quickly .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"came\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A NATO spokesman said : \" There 's no tracking mechanism to ensure they do n't fall into the wrong hands .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fall\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"For weeks , reporters scoured Alabama in search of pilots or anyone who might have remembered seeing Mr. Bush at the time he was serving in the National Guard there .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"scoured\", does the participant \"Alabama\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"'' Pakistan now has a large force deployed in Baluchistan which was not there before , '' says Lt. General David Barno .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"says\", does the participant \"Barno\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have lots of containers in there .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Dignitaries condemn the act but visit her bereaved family and the money flows .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"condemn\", does the participant \"act\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"It has two parts , both of which are timed for 90 seconds each and the differential between the resulting two scores determines the likelihood of having a learning disability or attention deficit disorder .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"timed\", does the participant \"both\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Just today I bought a medium rat for my beloved Ball Python Salazar ( name after Harry Potter ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"bought\", does the participant \"rat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The mysterious RAPHAEL Holinshed was named for the mysterious Neoplatonic Italian painter RAPHAEL Sanzio who painted _ St. George Fighting the Dragon _ ( 1504 - 06 )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"named\", does the participant \"Holinshed\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Cj and company did all that we ask and 10 times more .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"Cj\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I went to this urgent care center and was blown away with their service .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"went\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"TEXAS ROADHOUSE HAS VERY GOOD MEALS , THAT THE MEAT COMES RIGHT OFF THE BONES .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"HAS\", does the participant \"MEALS\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I called and asked about the price for hair updo and the receptionist or owner who aswered the phone refused to tell me , or even just give me an approximate price range .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"called\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a preorder and am even considering getting a second preorder to have multiple accounts .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The bill reduces ISS operations by $ 120 million due to the continued reduced capability of the ISS for at least half of FY05 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"reduces\", does the participant \"operations\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"You have two adjustment screws for up and down and right to left positions .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"You\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" Their screams changed , \" Dr. Fortier said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Fortier\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"China launches its second manned spaceflight mission\"\nQuestion: In the event \"launches\", does the participant \"China\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I use propane with a blower and a burner I built http://www.mikegigi.com/meltmetl.htm and http://www.mikegigi.com/firehole.htm\"\nQuestion: In the event \"use\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My father re-secured the petroleum assets of Kuwait in 1991 at a cost of sixty - one billion U.S. dollars ( $ 61,000,000,000 ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"re-secured\", does the participant \"father\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"On my panel , Loretta Lynch asked Reliant and Duke to supply her with the details of the contracts they cut to sell their power forward to marketers .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"asked\", does the participant \"Lynch\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I ordered a kid meal with a milk and found a bottle was half opened already .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ordered\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Justin , I have no knowledge of any bad faith actins Enron has pending in Texas but I will call Richard Sanders who manages domestic litgation here .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"manages\", does the participant \"Sanders\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I used my card to purchase a meal on the menu and the total on my receipt was $ 8.95 but when I went on line to check my transaction it show $ 10.74 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"used\", does the participant \"card\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I think this place is probably really great especially judging by the reviews on here .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" My first thought was to push it away , \" he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"push\", does the participant \"it\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The name was derived from the founder 's name Dr. Michael Cowpland .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"derived\", does the participant \"name\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}]